[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dr. Hannibal Lecter aids Clarice Starling in finding serial killer Buffalo Bill in which 1991 movie?", "correct_answer": "The Silence of the Lambs", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fugitive", "Basic Instinct", "The Usual Suspects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first geometry textbook which was written by the ancient Greek Euclid?", "correct_answer": "The Elements", "incorrect_answers": ["The Stoia", "The Principia", "The Academy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie, a high schoolers family and friends become convinced she is homosexual and send her to a residential therapy camp to cure her.", "correct_answer": "But Im a Cheerleader", "incorrect_answers": ["Chutney Popcorn", "Mumford", "Election"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character from the famous American sitcom Friends has the last name of Green?", "correct_answer": "Rachel", "incorrect_answers": ["Janice", "Chandler", "Ross and Monica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, winner of a life achievement Oscar, appeared in Alfred Hitchcocks movies: Rope, Vertigo, Rear Window and The Man Who Knew Too Much", "correct_answer": "James Stewart", "incorrect_answers": ["Cary Grant", "John Dall", "Cedric Hardwicke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color are the eggs in the popular Dr. Suess book with the character Sam-I-am that was published in 1960?", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "Blue", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that the word corn may refer to any cereal that is grown in a country?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the villains gigantic steel-toothed henchman in the movie The Spy Who Loved Me?", "correct_answer": "Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["Crushclaw", "Sabretooth", "Bigfoot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the nests of cave swifts consist of, which makes them edible and ranks them as a delicacy in Chinese cuisine?", "correct_answer": "Saliva", "incorrect_answers": ["Tender bamboo shoots", "Bones", "Dried insects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This member of Czech cuisine, consists of a marinated sausage, usually served with slices of Czech bread.", "correct_answer": "Utopenec", "incorrect_answers": ["Drstkova", "Polevka", "Knedliky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The seeds of which of these herbs are the key spice in Indian curries?", "correct_answer": "Coriander", "incorrect_answers": ["Tansy", "Costmary", "Thyme"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Old Royal Observatory, which is a part of the National Maritime Museum in London, was built in what year?", "correct_answer": "1675", "incorrect_answers": ["1765", "1567", "1657"]}]